import { createContext, useState } from "react";

const Init = {
  QuizHard: [
    {
      id: "1",
      question: "What is Reconciliation?",
      opt1: "The process through which React deletes the DOM.",
      opt2: "The process through which React updates and deletes the component.",
      opt3: "It is a process to set the state.",
      opt4: " The process through which React updates the DOM.",
      rightAnswer: " The process through which React updates the DOM.",
    },
    {
      id: "2",
      question: "Which are the correct phases of component lifecycle?",
      opt1: "Mounting: getDerivedStateFromProps(); Updating: componentWillUnmount(); Unmounting: shouldComponentUpdate()",
      opt2: "Mounting: componentWillUnmount(); Updating: render(); Unmounting: setState()",
      opt3: "Mounting: componentDidMount(); Updating: componentDidUpdate(); Unmounting: componentWillUnmount()",
      opt4: "Mounting: constructor(); Updating: getDerivedStateFromProps(); Unmounting: render()",
      rightAnswer:
        "Mounting: componentDidMount(); Updating: componentDidUpdate(); Unmounting: componentWillUnmount()",
    },
    {
      id: "3",
      question: " Controlled Component vs Uncontrolled Component?",
      opt1: "Controlled Components: every state mutation will have an associated handler function; Uncontrolled Components: store their own states internally",
      opt2: "Controlled Components: store their own states internally; Uncontrolled Components: every state mutation will have an associated handler function",
      opt3: "Controlled Components: A component who is so good at controlling itself; Uncontrolled Components: A component who has no idea how to control itself",
      opt4: "Controlled Components: every state mutation does not have an associated handler function; Uncontrolled Components: does not store their own states internally",
      rightAnswer:
        "Controlled Components: every state mutation will have an associated handler function; Uncontrolled Components: store their own states internally",
    },
    {
      id: "4",
      question: " State vs Props?",
      opt1: " Props is something that the parent doesn’t need and decide to throw around among other parents; State is the parent’s favorite child and something the component wants to nurture.",
      opt2: "Props get passed to the component using naming conventions, like a function parameter; State is managed within the component and holds some information that may change over the lifetime of the component.",
      opt3: "Props is a copy of real DOM; State is the definition of the real DOM.",
      opt4: " Prop is managed within the component and holds some information that may change over the lifetime of the component; State gets passed to the component, like a function parameter",
      rightAnswer:
        "Props get passed to the component using naming conventions, like a function parameter; State is managed within the component and holds some information that may change over the lifetime of the component.",
    },
    {
      id: "5",
      question: "What is the “key” prop??",
      opt1: "“Key” prop is just there to look pretty and there is no benefit whatsoever.",
      opt2: "“Key” prop is a way for React to identify a newly added item in a list and compare during the “diffing” algorithm.",
      opt3: " It is one of the attributes in HTML.",
      opt4: "All I know is that it is NOT commonly used in array.",
      rightAnswer:
        "“Key” prop is a way for React to identify a newly added item in a list and compare during the “diffing” algorithm.",
    },
    {
      id: "6",
      question: "Which of the following are the advantages of React.js?",
      opt1: "React.js can increase the application's performance with Virtual DOM.",
      opt2: "React.js is easy to integrate with other frameworks such as Angular, BackboneJS since it is only a view library.",
      opt3: "React.js can render both on client and server side.",
      opt4: "All of the above",
      rightAnswer: "All of the above",
    },
    {
      id: "7",
      question: "Which of the following is not a disadvantage of React.js?",
      opt1: "React.js has only a view layer. We have put your code for Ajax requests, events and so on.",
      opt2: "The library of React.js is pretty large.",
      opt3: "The JSX in React.js makes code easy to read and write.",
      opt4: "The learning curve can be steep in React.js.",
      rightAnswer: "The JSX in React.js makes code easy to read and write.",
    },
    {
      id: "8",
      question:
        " A class is a type of function, but instead of using the keyword function to initiate it, which keyword do we use?",
      opt1: "Constructor",
      opt2: "Class",
      opt3: "Object",
      opt4: "DataObject",
      rightAnswer: "Class",
    },
    {
      id: "9",
      question:
        "Which of the following acts as the input of a class-based component?",
      opt1: "Render",
      opt2: "Class",
      opt3: "Props",
      opt4: "Factory",
      rightAnswer: "Props",
    },
    {
      id: "10",
      question:
        "Which of the following keyword is used to create a class inheritance?",
      opt1: "Inherits",
      opt2: "Create",
      opt3: "This",
      opt4: "Extends",
      rightAnswer: "Extends",
    },
  ],
  QuizNormal: [
    {
      id: "1",
      question:
        "Which of the following is used in React.js to increase performance?",
      opt1: "Virtual DOM",
      opt2: "Orignal DOM",
      opt3: "Both A and B",
      opt4: "None of the above",
      rightAnswer: "Virtual DOM",
    },
    {
      id: "2",
      question: "What is ReactJS?",
      opt1: "Server-side framework",
      opt2: "User Interface Library",
      opt3: "Both A and B",
      opt4: "None of tyhe above",
      rightAnswer: "User Interface Library",
    },
    {
      id: "3",
      question:
        "Identify the one which is used to pass data to components from outside?",
      opt1: "Render with arguments",
      opt2: "setState",
      opt3: "PropTypes",
      opt4: "props",
      rightAnswer: "props",
    },
    {
      id: "4",
      question: "Who created React.js?",
      opt1: "Jordan Mike",
      opt2: "Jordan Walke",
      opt3: "Tim Lee",
      opt4: "Jordan Lee",
      rightAnswer: "Jordan Walke",
    },
    {
      id: "5",
      question: "What is Babel?",
      opt1: "Javascript Compiler",
      opt2: "Javascriptw Interpreter",
      opt3: "Javascript Transpiler",
      opt4: "None of the above",
      rightAnswer: "Javascript Compiler",
    },
    {
      id: "6",
      question: "Identify the command used to create a react app?",
      opt1: "npm install create-react",
      opt2: "npm i-create-react-app",
      opt3: "npx create-react-app",
      opt4: "npx Install create-react-app",
      rightAnswer: "npx create-react-app",
    },
    {
      id: "7",
      question:
        "Which of the following port is the default where webpack-dev-server runs?",
      opt1: "3300",
      opt2: "3303",
      opt3: "3000",
      opt4: "8080",
      rightAnswer: "8080",
    },
    {
      id: "8",
      question: "How many elements can a valid react component return?",
      opt1: "1",
      opt2: "2",
      opt3: "3",
      opt4: "4",
      rightAnswer: "1",
    },
    {
      id: "9",
      question: "A state in React.js is also known as?",
      opt1: "The internal storage of the component",
      opt2: "The external storage of the component",
      opt3: "Permanent storage",
      opt4: "All of the above",
      rightAnswer: "The internal storage of the component",
    },
    {
      id: "10",
      question:
        "Which of the following method is used to access the state of a component from inside of a member function?",
      opt1: "this.values",
      opt2: "this.getState()",
      opt3: "this.state",
      opt4: "this.prototype.stateValue",
      rightAnswer: "this.values",
    },
  ],
  QuizEasy: [
    {
      id: "1",
      question: "What do shell windows show in Python?",
      opt1: "Program Output",
      opt2: "Print Command",
      opt3: "Code",
      opt4: "IDLE",
      rightAnswer: "Program Output",
    },
    {
      id: "2",
      question: "What are people who write computer code?",
      opt1: "Programmers",
      opt2: "Professors",
      opt3: "Cryptographers",
      opt4: "Manufacturers",
      rightAnswer: "Programmers",
    },
    {
      id: "3",
      question: "What is computer coding?",
      opt1: "A radio show",
      opt2: "A list of functions",
      opt3: "Telling a computer what to do",
      opt4: "A TV show",
      rightAnswer: "Telling a computer what to do",
    },
    {
      id: "4",
      question:
        "What word describes characters that can be moved in a Scratch program?",
      opt1: "Imp",
      opt2: "Pixie",
      opt3: "Goblin",
      opt4: "Sprite",
      rightAnswer: "Sprite",
    },
    {
      id: "5",
      question: "Which of these does NOT run using a computer program?",
      opt1: "Bicycle",
      opt2: "Rocket",
      opt3: "Train",
      opt4: "Car",
      rightAnswer: "Bicycle",
    },
    {
      id: "6",
      question: "How many types of windows does Python use?",
      opt1: "Five",
      opt2: "Four",
      opt3: "One",
      opt4: "Two",
      rightAnswer: "Two",
    },
    {
      id: "7",
      question: "Which of these is a programming language?",
      opt1: "Scratch",
      opt2: "Bite",
      opt3: "Itch",
      opt4: "Gnaw",
      rightAnswer: "Scratch",
    },
    {
      id: "8",
      question: "Which of these is NOT a programming language?",
      opt1: "Java",
      opt2: "Banana",
      opt3: "Ruby",
      opt4: "Python",
      rightAnswer: "Banana",
    },
    {
      id: "9",
      question:
        "What word describes the set of instructions that computers need to do work?",
      opt1: "Blueprint",
      opt2: "Agenda",
      opt3: "Synopsis",
      opt4: "Program",
      rightAnswer: "Program",
    },
    {
      id: "10",
      question: "What symbols are used to makeup the Python language?",
      opt1: "Runes",
      opt2: "Words",
      opt3: "Heiroglyphics",
      opt4: "Sprites",
      rightAnswer: "Words",
    },
  ],
};

const Store = createContext(Init);
export default Store;

const StoreFunction = (props) => {
  const [QuizNormal, setQuizNormal] = useState(Init.QuizNormal);
  const [QuizHard, setQuizHard] = useState(Init.QuizHard);
  const [QuizEasy, setQuizEasy] = useState(Init.QuizEasy);

  return (
    <Store.Provider
      value={{
        ...Init,
        QuizNormal: [...QuizNormal],
        QuizHard: [...QuizHard],
        QuizEasy: [...QuizEasy],
      }}
    >
      {props.children}
    </Store.Provider>
  );
};

export { StoreFunction };
